Still armed. Still dangerous. Still got it.
RED is a action, adventure, comedy film directed by Robert Schwentke.
After surviving an assault from a squad of hit men, retired CIA black ops
agent Frank Moses reassembles his old team for an all-out war.
Frank reunites with old Joe, crazy Marvin and wily Victoria to
uncover a massive conspiracy that threatens their lives.
Only their expert training will allow them to survive a
near-impossible mission -- breaking into CIA headquarters.
Frank Moses, played by Bruce Willis.
Marvin Boggs, played by John Malkovich.
Joe Matheson, played by Morgan Freeman.
Victoria, played by Helen Mirren.
Sarah Ross, played by Mary-Louise Parker.
William Cooper, played by Karl Urban.
Red is a 2010 American action comedy film directed by Robert Schwentke, based
on the comic book series by Warren Ellis and Cully Hamner.
The film stars Bruce Willis, Morgan Freeman, John Malkovich, Helen Mirren, Karl Urban,
Mary-Louise Parker, Brian Cox, Julian McMahon and Richard Dreyfuss.
The plot involves Frank Moses, a former black-ops agent who reunites with his
old team to capture an assassin who has vowed to kill him.
Red premiered at the Fantastic Fest on September 29, 2010, and was released
in the United States on October 15, by Summit Entertainment.
The film received generally positive reviews from critics and was nominated for Best
Motion Picture – Musical or Comedy at the 68th Golden Globe Awards.
A sequel, Red 2, was released in 2013.
The film explores themes of assassin, central intelligence agency
(cia), undercover agent, kidnapping, assault rifle.
The tone is lighthearted and intense.